export default data = [
  {
      question: "With his excellent social skills, Steven has been ______ as a great communicator by all his colleagues.",
      options: ["diagnosed","exploited","perceived","concerned"],
      correct_option: "perceived"
  },
  {
      question: "When you enter a building, be sure to look behind you and hold the door open for someone coming through the same door. It is a common ______ in many cultures.",
      options: ["process","courtesy","acceptance","operation"],
      correct_option: "courtesy"
  },
  {
      question: "The telephone has changed beyond ______ in recent years. In both form and function, it has become totally different from what it was before.",
      options: ["recognition","possession","prevention","appreciation"],
      correct_option: "recognition"
  },
  {
      question: "Though Jack has moved out of his parents’ house, he is ______ dependent on them still. They send him a check every month for his living expenses.",
      options: ["radically","physically","financially","politically"],
      correct_option: "financially"
  },
  {
      question: "If you want to keep your computer from being attacked by new viruses, you need to constantly renew and ______ your anti-virus software.",
      options: ["confirm","overlook","esteem","update"],
      correct_option: "update"
  },
  {
      question: "Many factors may explain why people are addicted to the Internet. One factor ______ to this phenomenon is the easy access to the Net.",
      options: ["advancing","occurring","responding","contributing"],
      correct_option: "contributing"
  },
  {
      question: "We were ______ awaiting the results of the school’s annual English drama contest. Our class won the first place last year, and we certainly wanted to win again this year.",
      options: ["consciously","anxiously","fortunately","competently"],
      correct_option: "anxiously"
  },
  {
      question: "Tropical rainforests are home to about one million plant and animal species. If the rainforests disappear, many of these species will become       .",
      options: ["extinct","hostile","mature","intimate"],
      correct_option: "extinct"
  },
  {
      question: "An honest person is faithful to his promise. Once he makes a ______ , he will not go back on his own word.",
      options: ["prescription","commitment","frustration","transcript"],
      correct_option: "commitment"
  },
  {
      question: "The new computer game Wii provides us with an ______ way of exercising. People now may play sports in their living rooms, which was unimaginable before.",
      options: ["outgoing","urgent","aggressive","innovative"],
      correct_option: "innovative"
  },
]